<chapter xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook"
	 version="5.0"
	 xml:id="officer-duties-and-roles">
  <title>Office Duties and Roles</title>

  <section>
    <title>Chair</title>
    <para>
      An ACM/FSG Chair position can be very rewarding but often
      requires the most work.  In the event that another officer is
      busy, needs you to pick up one of their duties, or even forgets
      then it is your responsibility to pick up their slack.

      Following is a shortened list of duties that the Chair is
      responsible for:
      <itemizedlist>
	<listitem>
	  <para>
	    First and foremost, making sure everyone else is
	    doing their job.
	  </para>
	  </listitem>
	<listitem>
	  <para>
	    Query potential speakers.
	  </para>
	</listitem>
	<listitem>
	  <para>
	    Set meeting dates/time.
	  </para>
	</listitem>
	<listitem>
	<para>
	  Create and post meeting fliers.
	</para>
	</listitem>
	<listitem>
	  <para>
	    Email the appropriate lists with meeting announcements.
	  </para>
	  </listitem>
	<listitem>
	  <para>Leading meetings and introducing speakers.
	</para>
	</listitem>
      </itemizedlist>
    </para>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Vice Chair</title>
    <para>
      In the event that the Chair cannot take care of certain tasks,
      be ready to pick them up!  This could be anything from running a
      meeting to posting the flyers.
    </para>
    <para>
      You will also assist the Chair by running meetings or
      introducing speakers.
    </para>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Secretary</title>
    <para>
      The Treasurer is responsible for the following tasks:
      <itemizedlist>
	<listitem>
	  <para>At every meeting, collect a list of attendees. Give a
	  copy to the Treasurer so that they can give it, along with
	  the pizza receipt, to the appropriate staff member.
	</para>
	</listitem>
      </itemizedlist>
    </para>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Treasurer</title>
    <para>
      The Treasurer is responsible for the following tasks:
      <itemizedlist>
	<listitem>
	  <para>	  
	    Reporting the club's funds at the beginning of every
	    meeting.
	  </para>
	</listitem>
	<listitem>
	  <para>
	    Ordering pizza for the meetings.
	  </para>
	  </listitem>
	<listitem>
	  <para>
	  Making sure that there will be plates, cups, and napkins at
	  the meeting.
	  </para>
	</listitem>
	<listitem>
	  <para>Signing and keeping receipts to give to the
	  appropriate staff member.
	</para>
	</listitem>
      </itemizedlist>
    </para>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Webmaster</title>
    <para>
      <itemizedlist>
	<listitem>
	<para>
	  Post events on the acm website http://wvu.acm.org
	</para>
	</listitem>
	<listitem>
	<para>
	  Speak to the chair to gain access to the sites administration.
	</para>
	</listitem>
      </itemizedlist>
    </para>
  </section>

</chapter>
