<preface xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook"
        version="5.0"
        xmlns:xl="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
        xml:id="preface">

  <title>Preface</title>

  <para>
    If you're reading this then you are now an officer (or should be)
    in the WVU ACM or FSG.
  </para>

  <para>
    You're not only a part of one of the most active and successful
    clubs on campus, you're taking a role in leading it. In just two
    years we were able to take a club of humble origins and turn it in
    the club to be watched on the Engineering campus. We're in the
    business of making things happen and you will be too.
  </para>
  <para>
    In just the past several years, we've hosted events such as
    Richard Stallman's talk on Copyright, John Perry Barlow's
    discussion on political unrest in the Middle East, and Corey
    Haines Test-Driven Development code retreat. Through FSG, we were
    able to get free alternatives installed in campus computer labs.
  </para>
  <para>
    As an officer of ACM &amp; FSG, you have a responsibility to keep
    the fire burning; to keep organizing awesome events that engage
    students and get them asking questions. Perhaps you'll change
    their point of view or introduce them to ideas that change their
    lives.
  </para>
  <section>
    <title>The Free Software Group</title>
    <para>
      The Free Software Group (FSG) was founded in 2008 as an
      organization separate to the ACM. That year we realized that we
      could accomplish so much more if we worked together as sister
      organizations. An article was featured in the Daily Athenaeum to
      cover FSG's founding.
      <footnote>
      <para>
	http://www.thedaonline.com/newest-student-org-connects-to-campus-1.700949
      </para>
      </footnote>
    </para>
    <para>
      Seeing as the ACM is a national organization based mainly on
      research in the field of Computer Science and Engineering, a club
      needed to exist to promote Free Software on campus and host events
      centered on Free Software.
    </para>    
    
    <example xml:id="fsg-manifesto">
      <title>The WVU Free Software Group Manifesto</title>
      <para>
	Raise Awareness, distribute, and encourage the 
	adoption and installation of free software to the 
	Student Body, Morgantown Community, and in 
	Campus Computing Facilities.
      </para>
    </example>
    
    <para>
      ACM &amp; FSG have different goals as organizations. While ACM
      &amp; FSG work very closely to plan events, it is important that
      the two clubs remain separate entities. Free Software doesn't
      appeal to every Computer Science student on campus which is why
      the ACM pushes forward events that will appeal to the majority
      of LCSEE.
    </para>
    
    <mediaobject>
      <imageobject>
	<imagedata fileref="images/fsg_founders.jpg"/>
      </imageobject>
      <caption>
	<para>
	  The founding officers of WVU FSG. Left to right; Tim
	  'Shaggy' Bielawa, Bryant Doss, Greg Belknap, and Andrew
	  Butcher.
	</para>
      </caption>
    </mediaobject>
  </section>
</preface>