<chapter xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook"
	 version="5.0"
	 xml:id="yearly-responsibilities">
  <title>Yearly Responsibilites</title>

  <section>
    <title>Fall Semester</title>
    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
	<para>
	  <emphasis role="bold">Freshman EngineerFEST</emphasis>, occurs around the
	  second week of classes. The point of this event is to spark
	  interest in joining ACM to incoming freshman. The chair of the
	  club will most likely receive an email about booking a table
	  for Freshman EngineerFEST. If they don't, then be sure to ask
	  around Freshman Engineering. Be sure to bring a sign up sheet
	  so that new students can jot down their emails. It's also a
	  good idea to bring an info sheet so that students can read a
	  little bit more about the clubs and check out our site. Make a
	  big poster if you have time.
	</para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
	<para>
	  <emphasis role="bold">First Meeting</emphasis>, the first meeting is
	  listed because it sets the tone for the rest of the semester.
	  More people are going to come to this meeting than any other
	  meeting. This meeting should occur soon following Freshman
	  EngineerFEST.  Follow meeting protocol and everything will be
	  great.  Be sure to re-iterate what the club is about and have
	  a banging speaker for this meeting.
	</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Spring Semester</title>
    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
	<para>
	  <emphasis role="bold">Big Event</emphasis>, historically,
	  ACM/FSG has a large event in Spring around February. It
	  usually takes up to this point to have planned and
	  coordinated with a speaker to get them here.
	</para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
	<para>
	  <emphasis role="bold">Officer Election</emphasis>, it is
	  very important that officer elections occur before the end
	  of the Spring semester so that everyone isn't busy with
	  their finals and can't attent the election. This happened in
	  Spring 2011. It is also important to elect a group at this
	  time so that they can plan and get to know eachother over
	  the Summer months.
	</para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
	<para>
	  <emphasis role="bold">Annual Reports w/ ACM
	  Headquarters</emphasis>, late in the Spring semster usually
	  the club chair will get an email from the department asking
	  them to manage the annual report. This report includes
	  several sections including current officers (all of which
	  must be registered with the ACM to be credited), finances
	  (records should have been kept), current members (a list
	  should have been maintained), and upcoming events
	  (brainstorm). To access the annual report, contact the
	  faculty advisor of the ACM.
	</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>
  </section>
</chapter>